export const questions = {
  Sports: [
    {
      question: "Which national team won the world cup 1998 ?",
      choices: ["Brazil", "Italy", "Germany", "France", "England"],
      correctanswer: "France",
    },
    {
      question:
        "Who's the highest scroing player from Liverpool in the Premier League ?",
      choices: ["Rooney", "Scholes", "Giggs", "Salah", "Mane"],
      correctanswer: "Salah",
    },
    {
      question: "Which team is the most winning of the world cup ?",
      choices: ["France", "Brazil", "England", "Germany"],
      correctanswer: "Brazil",
    },
    {
      question: "Who's the highest paid fottballer in history",
      choices: ["Messi", "Maradona", "Chrsitiano Ronaldo", "Romario, Zidan"],
      correctanswer: "alexander fleming",
    },
  ],
  Music: [
    {
      question: "Which singer did the longest music tour ?",
      choices: ["Madonna", "Michael Jackson", "Mark Antony", "Nelly", "Eminem"],
      correctanswer: "Michael Jackson",
    },
    {
      question: "Who invented the Ann MArie musical Symphony ?",
      choices: ["Beethoven", "Bach", "Tchaikovesky", "Mozart"],
      correctanswer: "Bach",
    },
  ],
  Science: [
    {
      question:
        "Who is the only human being to win 2 noble prizes in 2 different science ?",
      choices: [
        "albert einstein",
        "nicola tesla",
        "Graham Bill",
        "marie curie",
      ],
      correctanswer: "marie curie",
    },
    {
      question: "the scientist with the most inventions in recent history ?",
      choices: [
        "Thomas Edison",
        "archimedes",
        "nicola tesla",
        "michael faraday",
      ],
      correctanswer: "nicola tesla",
    },
    {
      question:
        "who's the first scientist to invent the concept of visual reflection (camera) ?",
      choices: [
        "rosalind franklin",
        "james d watson",
        "alhazin",
        "alexander fleming",
      ],
      correctanswer: "alhazin",
    },
    {
      question: "who's the scientist to invent the first antibiotic in history",
      choices: ["carl yung", "carl sagan", "alexander fleming", "carl gauss"],
      correctanswer: "alexander fleming",
    },
  ],
};
